<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Hearthstone Property Management</string>

    <string name="sell">sell</string>

    <string name="rent">rent</string>

    <string name="news">news</string>

    <string name="contactString">contact</string>

    <string name="purchaseString">buy</string>

    <string name="emailContent">Good after noon william i would like to give you a million dollars</string>

    <string name="emailSubject">Regarding your properties</string>

    <string name="beds">Beds</string>

    <string name="baths">Baths</string>

    <string name="square_feet">SQ feet</string>

    <string name="View_of_house">View of house</string>

    <string name="available_houses_to_purchase">buy buy buy</string>

    <string name="available_rentals">rent rent rent</string>

    <string name="news_header">news</string>

    <string name="unavailable">unavailable</string>

    <string name="min_price">Min Price</string>

    <string name="max_price">Max Price</string>

    <string name="price_range">Select Price Range</string>

    <string name="required_features">required features</string>

    <string name="sq_ft_range">SQ. FT Range</string>

    <string name="prompt_no_min">no min</string>

    <string name="prompt_no_max">no Max</string>

    <string name="any">any</string>

    <string name="fireplace">fireplace</string>

    <string name="garage">Garage</string>

    <string name="property_type">property type</string>

    <string name="house">house</string>

    <string name="condo">condo</string>

    <string name="house_condo">house/condo</string>

    <string name="view_all">view all</string>

    <string name="rental_propety_search">Rental Property Search</string>

    <string name="search">search</string>

    <string name="location">location</string>

    <string name="clovis">Clovis</string>

    <string name="portales">Portales</string>

    <string name="additional_options">additional options</string>

    <string name="waxLabel">History of Sealing Wax</string>

    <string name="sealingWaxP1">Would you be interested int he history of seals, which have been traced back to Anno Domini 930?</string>
    <string name="sealingWaxP2">Since the time immemorial, the seal has served as a stamp of indisputable authenticity, just as a signature is accepted in the world today. The use of seals can be traced back to the Old Testament, where it mentions that Jezabel used Ahab\'s seal to counterfeit important documents. Seals were first used by Kings and governments long ago.</string>
    <string name="sealingWaxP3">The first Great Seal of England was that of Edward the Confessor, impressions of which can still be found. New laws and proclamations required the authoritative stamp of a seal. During Medieval Times, almost everyone had their own Seal, but Royalty would own several, including their own "Great Seal", as well as seals for all their courts and officials. It was common practice to destroy a person\'s seal once the owner died; hence the reason so few original seals have survived.</string>
    <string name="sealingWaxP4">Official Seals of the Crown were often handed over with great ceremony, and in Medieval Times the size of the motif of the Seal conveyed an image of the status of its owner. Early motifs were equestrian or heraldic in nature, or showed the owner in various pursuits like hunting or doing battle. William the Conqueror used an equestrian seal showing him armed and ready for battle.</string>
    <string name="sealingWaxP5">Long ago, betrothals were pre-arranged therefore true words of love were secretly written and the envelop\'s contents was secured by a wax seal, so that the recipient could be assured that their passion would be unknown to others. A broken wax seal implied broken trust…and no person of integrity would tamper with a wax emblem.</string>
    <string name="sealingWaxP6">Benjamin Franklin, John Adams and Thomas Jefferson created the first seal of the United States on July 4th, 1776, immediately after the Declaration of Independence was signed. Congress realized the necessity of such a seal for the newly established nation.</string>





</resources>
